<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bastien Boutonnet</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Bastien Boutonnet</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 09:34:14 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hello Hello World</title><link>/homepage/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 19:36:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>/homepage/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m Bastien Boutonnet, a lead data scientist at soda.io and an Amsterdam resident.
I like to build and maintain open-source projects and tools for data practitioners, which I mostly do under the bitpicky umbrella.
When I don&amp;rsquo;t write code, I produce music under several aliases one of which is accuraat and play other people&amp;rsquo;s music to other dancing people in clubs (well, before there was a pandemic that is).
THE SOCIALS Twitter: @B_superhero Sometimes I tweet interesting stuff GitHub: @bastienboutonnet For my personal projects.</description></item><item><title>How to Stay on Top of Slack?</title><link>/posts/stay-on-top-of-slack/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 09:34:14 +0100</pubDate><guid>/posts/stay-on-top-of-slack/</guid><description>credits Getty Images TL;DR Use and abuse reminders! You can jump to the how to section if you are already sold on the idea.
Slack has become one of the most popular workplace messaging platforms these days. This is especially true in newly established organisations. Being a really big proponent of using all things modern and having struggled all my life with finding a way to like email, I quickly embraced Slack as my favourite messaging app.</description></item><item><title>Document dbt Models the easy way with dbt-sugar</title><link>/posts/document-dbt-models-with-dbt-sugar/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 14:28:18 +0100</pubDate><guid>/posts/document-dbt-models-with-dbt-sugar/</guid><description>Would you like your documentation workflow to look something like this? Now it&amp;rsquo;s possible with dbt-sugar
NOTE: This tool is still pretty new and in alpha/beta stage, but we think you can start testing it and helping us making it better along the way.
Contribute on GitHub Become part of the community by joining our Discord server If you&amp;rsquo;re a user of dbt chances are you&amp;rsquo;re already are on a great path to making your data team successful at iterating and serving analytical value to your business.</description></item></channel></rss>